http://www.apec-econ.ca/privacy-policy/

Atlantic Canada’s independent voice on economic issuesFrançaisHomeAbout APECMembershipEventsPublicationsResearch ThemesClean GrowthEU & CETADigital Technology FirmsCOVID-19 in Atlantic CanadaIndigenous ResearchLooking AheadHome »Privacy PolicyThere are 0 items in your shopping cart!Member LoginGet Email UpdatesFollow UsConnect with UsPrivacy Policy
The Atlantic Provinces Economic Council (APEC) is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We have developed this privacy policy to advise you of our personal information handling practices and of your rights in relation to any personal information you share with us.
Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you other than business contact information.Collection of information
We collect personal information from members, individuals registering for our conferences and seminars, individuals presenting at the conferences and seminars, individuals ordering copies of our publications, and individuals requesting email updates regarding APEC publications and events.
The information collected is limited to the information required to process the membership application or conference registration, to fill an order for a publication, or to add the individual to the email subscriber list. The information collected for these purposes includes email addresses, names, addresses, telephone number, fax number and credit card information, as applicable.
Where individuals use our website to order publications or register for conferences or other events, their credit card payment is handled by an outside credit card processing company with whom we have a contractual arrangement. We do not collect or see credit card information when we process an online order or registration.
We do not collect any personal information from visitors to our website unless personal information is submitted to us when an individual purchases a publication, membership or registers for an event online.Use of Personal Information
The personal information you provide the Atlantic Provinces Economic Council (APEC) is used only to send publications to our members, to notify members of upcoming events and opportunities and to remind members to renew their membership.  We also use the contact information of conference and event registrants to provide you with further information about the conference or event. Contact information for individuals requesting to receive email updates from APEC is used to notify you of publications and upcoming seminars and events.
Our membership list is published in our Annual Report and is available on our website.  Any member who does not wish to appear on the membership list in the Annual Report or on the website may so specify on the membership application form or may contact our privacy officer at any time to request that their name not be published with the list of members.
Under no circumstances will APEC disclose, rent, sell, barter or share the personal information we collect from our members, conference registrants or individuals purchasing our publications unless required by law.Safeguarding your information
Any personal information that you share with APEC is kept physically and electronically separate with access limited to staff that require it to perform necessary job functions. We use a firewall to protect our computer files.
We insure that the company which processes online credit card payments from our website has in place similar privacy protections and that it does not use your personal information for any purposes other than processing your online credit card payment.
We retain your personal information for only as long as we may reasonable need the information to provide membership or other services to you, to respond to complaints or inquiries, and to fulfill auditing and other legal requirements.Web Site Links
Our website contains links to other sites.  Our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other organizations or for any personal information that may be collected when you leave our site to visit a linked site.Your Rights
You have a right, subject to certain statutory exceptions, to review the personal information we have collected about you and to have any errors in your personal information corrected. We will respond to your written inquiry in a reasonable period of time and in any event within thirty days unless an extension is required.  You may need to provide sufficient information to allow us to respond to your request.Changes to the Privacy Statement
APEC reserves the right to make minor modifications to this Privacy Statement in the interest of further enhancing the protection of personal information. If any substantial changes are made, APEC will post a notice on its website.How to Contact About Your Information
If you receive publications or notifications from us which you no longer wish to receive you have a right at any time to request that we remove you from our mailing list.  Simply contact our privacy officer.
Please direct questions and inquiries about your personal information to our Privacy Officer at the following address:
Privacy Officer
Atlantic Provinces Economic Council
5121 Sackville Street, Suite 500
Halifax, NS
B3J 1K1
Or email us at:
MenuHomeFrançaisAbout APECMembershipResearch ThemesPublicationsEngagementEventsExtrasSite MapReturn/Refund PolicyTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContact Us5121 Sackville St. Suite 500Halifax, Nova Scotia B3J 1K1Phone:(902) 422-6516Fax:Fax: (902) 429-6803Email:info@apec-econ.caCopyright © 2020 - Atlantic Provinces Economic Council. All rights reserved.Website Design by Cossette
